<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on The Cat Life</title>
    <link>https://blissman.ca/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on The Cat Life</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 23 Apr 2021 06:41:40 -0400</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://blissman.ca/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Dad&#39;s Back!</title>
      <link>https://blissman.ca/posts/dads-back/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Apr 2021 06:41:40 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blissman.ca/posts/dads-back/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s been about a week since our new neighbours moved in, and while we had seen mum busting her foxy little butt to feed the kits, we hadn&amp;rsquo;t seen dad. As red foxes are known to be monogamous, we speculated that maybe something had happened to him. Was he attacked by an off-leash dog? Should we have bylaw come by and put up some signs and hand out some fines? Or maybe this particular fox wasn&amp;rsquo;t so monogamous?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Second Winter</title>
      <link>https://blissman.ca/posts/second-winter/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Apr 2021 17:30:05 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blissman.ca/posts/second-winter/</guid>
      <description>This week marked &amp;ldquo;second winter&amp;rdquo;: Canada&amp;rsquo;s annual surprise snowfall in Spring. Each year, Canadians young and old remark that they &amp;ldquo;can&amp;rsquo;t believe this is happening&amp;rdquo; and that &amp;ldquo;it doesn&amp;rsquo;t usually snow this late, does it?&amp;rdquo; (in spite of the long-standing tradition). I suppose it&amp;rsquo;s a kindness of human memory to forget the trauma.
It&amp;rsquo;s been a few days since I&amp;rsquo;ve seen my new neighbours, with only paw prints in the snow to confirm their continued residence.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The New Neighbours</title>
      <link>https://blissman.ca/posts/the-new-neighbours/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Apr 2021 20:17:07 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blissman.ca/posts/the-new-neighbours/</guid>
      <description>With the pandemic in full swing, and the Canadian housing market hotter than ever, there&amp;rsquo;s been a flurry of action in my neighbourhood as houses get bought and sold at a dizzying rate. A common concern with families coming in is whether it&amp;rsquo;s going to disrupt your way of living. Will they be noisy? Will they be rude? Will they have tacky sense of design? Sometimes though, you get lucky.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>An Indoor Cat in the Forest</title>
      <link>https://blissman.ca/posts/an-indoor-cat-in-the-forest/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Jul 2018 14:05:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blissman.ca/posts/an-indoor-cat-in-the-forest/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ve always self-identified my spirit animal as the noble raccoon. Something about its bandit face and clever hands finding discarded food (or trash) always spoke to me (#4age4lyfe). Those who know me best however tell me that I am in reality much closer to a bougie indoor cat; preferring my beds soft and my plumbing indoors.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Amazing World of Nature</title>
      <link>https://blissman.ca/posts/the-amazing-world-of-nature/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Jul 2018 18:06:48 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blissman.ca/posts/the-amazing-world-of-nature/</guid>
      <description>I met the shyest little cutie today. I barely managed to snap a few shots before she ran by me!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Welcome!</title>
      <link>https://blissman.ca/posts/welcome/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Jul 2018 21:41:36 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blissman.ca/posts/welcome/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to my site! I know what you&amp;rsquo;re wondering: yes, it&amp;rsquo;ll mostly be cat photos. I hope you&amp;rsquo;re into that.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
